<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sustainability on ГО “Громадська синергія”</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/ukr/tags/sustainability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sustainability on ГО “Громадська синергія”</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>ukr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/ukr/tags/sustainability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prof. Dluhopolskyi Presents NEET Integration Insights at Ljubljana Conference</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ukr/post-copy/post-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ukr/post-copy/post-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Exploring Inclusive Education and Digital Communication: Dr. Oleksandr Dluhopolskyi Presents AFID Project Results to Master&amp;rsquo;s Students in Educational Institution Management&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On May 16, 2024, as part of the Erasmus+ AFID project, Dr. Sc. (Economics), Prof.  Oleksandr Dluhopolskyi, Executive Director of the NGO &amp;ldquo;Civic Synergy&amp;rdquo;, presented a report at an international conference at the Ljubljana School of Business (Ljubljana, Slovenia) on the topic “NEETs Integration into Social and Economic Activity in the Context of Sustainability”. The presentation for an international audience (over 100 participants from various countries) focused on the importance of integrating NEET groups, including by involving them in online courses on various platforms to enhance their sustainable development competencies (example of AFID). As a result of the presentation, an article was published in the international journal Agora International Journal of Economical Sciences (&lt;a href=&#34;https://univagora.ro/jour/index.php/aijes/article/view/6708%29&#34;&gt;https://univagora.ro/jour/index.php/aijes/article/view/6708)&lt;/a&gt;.&#xA;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
