<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ukrainian HEIs on NGO “Civic Synergy”</title>
    <link>https://vampire7432804732985734985743948.github.io/NGO-page/tags/ukrainian-heis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ukrainian HEIs on NGO “Civic Synergy”</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vampire7432804732985734985743948.github.io/NGO-page/tags/ukrainian-heis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Digital Skills and Inclusion: Insights from AFID Training</title>
      <link>https://vampire7432804732985734985743948.github.io/NGO-page/post/post-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vampire7432804732985734985743948.github.io/NGO-page/post/post-7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Advancing Digital Skills and Inclusive Online Education: Professors Kozyuk and Dluhopolskyi Join International AFID Erasmus+CBHE Training&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Within the framework of the AFID Erasmus+CBHE project, Head of the Department of Economics and Economic Theory, Doctor of Economics, Professor V. Kozyuk and Professor of the Department of Economics and Economic Theory, Executive Director of the NGO “Public Synergy”, Doctor of Economics O. Dlugopolskyi took part in the training “Digital Skills for Teachers and Administrative Staff” (April 8-11, 2024). The training was also attended by representatives of several Ukrainian HEIs (DTEK, Lviv Polytechnic National University, HNUE named after S. Kuznets, NTU Dnipro Polytechnic), the University of Alcalá (Spain) and the University of Lisbon (Portugal).&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Participants had the opportunity to familiarize themselves with and practice:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Preliminary Results of the ERASMUS&#43; AFID Project with Ukrainian HEIs</title>
      <link>https://vampire7432804732985734985743948.github.io/NGO-page/post/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vampire7432804732985734985743948.github.io/NGO-page/post/post-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dissemination of information about the preliminary results of the ERASMUS+ AFID (Academic Freedom and Inclusion through Digitalization) project among Ukrainian HEIs&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On February 21, 2024, as part of the implementation of the Erasmus+ AFID project, the Faculty of Economics and Management of WUNU (West Ukrainian  National University) held a training for teachers &amp;ldquo;Implementation of inclusiveness in online courses&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;The training was conducted by the Executive Director of the NGO &amp;ldquo;Civic Synergy&amp;rdquo;, Dr. Sc. (Economics), Prof. Oleksandr Dlugopolsky, who spoke about the mission, purpose, goals and current results of the AFID project for university teachers.&#xA;Special attention was paid to the opportunities for students and teachers provided by the project to strengthen the inclusiveness of asynchronous online courses, the use of specific digital tools in teaching and learning.&#xA;Important thematic directions of international cooperation for the future are outlined, which are designed to contribute to the solution of problems and challenges faced by all participants of the educational process in Ukraine regarding the development of inclusive education&#xA;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
